MICHAEL SUNDAY

Lagos State, Nigeria
Cell Phone: +234 813 445 1342

Porfolio: https://my-portfolio-view.vercel.app/

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/michael-sunday-18b5a4267

GitHub: https://github.com/Mikeonweb

PERSONAL PROFILE

A front-end developer with 1 year of experience.

I build responsive, scalable, and user friendly websites for individuals and businesses that best represent who they are and what they do. I work with HTML, CSS, and Javascript. I also work very well with technologies like GitHub.

I'm highly disciplined, very resourceful, love to work with people, and I am a team player.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Betty Distribution 2021 – 2022

Position Held: Warehouse Manager

 I oversaw all areas of warehouse operations, inventory management, order fulfilment and logistics coorderation.

Fitness & Sports Solution

2014 - 2019

Position Held: Installer/Sales Executive

• I advised new and existing customers on the workout equipment, that is suitable for their workout routine and fitness goals and I carried, out installation of gym equipments for customers and display purpose.

EDUCATIONAL QUALIFICATIONS WITH DATE

Christ Hill College 2007 – 2013

Secondary School Certificate Examination (SSCE)

Amuwo Odofin Community Primary School 2001 – 2006

First School Leaving Certificate (FSLC)

SKILLS

- · Good communication and interpersonal skills.
- Positive attitude to team work.
- Enthusiastic, resilience, confidence, and result oriented.
- · Social media marketing and engagement
- Publishing experience (WordPress)
- Research & fact-checking

HOBBIES

Coding, Writing, Listening to music, Singing.

REFEREES

To be provided upon request